

export const Questions = [
    {
        
        question: "What network topology uses a single cable to connect nodes?",
        optionA: "Bus Topology",
        optionB: "Star Topology",
        optionC: "Mesh Topology",
        optionD: "Ring Topology",
        answer: "optionA"
    },
    {
        question: "Computer systems on a network are referred to as _______",
        optionA: "PCs",
        optionB: "Nodes",
        optionC: "Servers",
        optionD: "Rings",
        answer: "optionB" 
    },
    {
        
        question: "Hybrids network uses a combination of any _______ or more topologies.",
        optionA: "One",
        optionB: "None",
        optionC: "Two",
        optionD: "One and a half",
        answer: "optionC"
    },
    {
        
        question: "On a bus topology, terminators eliminate the possibility of _______________",
        optionA: "Crosstalk",
        optionB: "Noise",
        optionC: "Signal Bounce",
        optionD: "EMI",
        answer: "optionC"
    },
    {
        question: "What type of device is used at either end of a bus network?",
        optionA: "Terminator",
        optionB: "Ohmmeter",
        optionC: "Transceiver",
        optionD: "Track",
        answer: "optionA"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these is a standard interface for serial data transmission?",
        optionA: "ASCII",
        optionB: "RS232C",
        optionC: "2",
        optionD: "Centronics",
        answer: "optionB"
    },
    {
        question: " Which type of topology is best suited for large businesses which must carefully control and coordinate the operation of distributed branch outlets?",
        optionA: "Ring",
        optionB: "Local Area",
        optionC: "Hierarchichal",
        optionD: "Star",
        answer: "optionD"
    },
    {
        question: " Which of the following transmission directions listed is not a legitimate channel?",
        optionA: "Simplex",
        optionB: "Half Duplex",
        optionC: "Full Duplex",
        optionD: "Double Duplex",
        answer: "optionD"
    },
    {
        question: "Parity bits are used for which of the following purposes?",
        optionA: "Encryption of data",
        optionB: "To transmit faster",
        optionC: "To detect errors",
        optionD: "To identify the user",
        answer: "optionC"
    },
    {
        
        question: "What kind of transmission medium is most appropriate to carry data in a computer network that is exposed to electrical interferences?",
        optionA: "Unshielded twisted pair",
        optionB: "Optical fiber",
        optionC: "Coaxial cable",
        optionD: "Microwave",
        answer: "optionB"
    },
    {
        question: "A collection of hyperlinked documents on the internet forms the ?.?",
        optionA: "World Wide Web (WWW)",
        optionB: "E-mail system",
        optionC: "Mailing list",
        optionD: "Hypertext markup language",
        answer: "optionA"
    },
    {
        question: "The location of a resource on the internet is given by its?",
        optionA: "Protocol",
        optionB: "URL",
        optionC: "E-mail address",
        optionD: "ICQ",
        answer: "optionB"
    },
    {
        question: "The term HTTP stands for?",
        optionA: "Hyper terminal tracing program",
        optionB: "Hypertext tracing protocol",
        optionC: "Hypertext transfer protocol",
        optionD: "Hypertext transfer program",
        answer: "optionC"
    },
    {
        question: "A proxy server is used as the computer?",
        optionA: "with external access",
        optionB: "acting as a backup",
        optionC: "performing file handling",
        optionD: "accessing user permissions",
        answer: "optionA"
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following would breach the integrity of a system?",
        optionA: "Looking the room to prevent theft",
        optionB: "Full access rights for all users",
        optionC: "Fitting the system with an anti-theft device",
        optionD: "Protecting the device against willful or accidental damage",
        answer: "optionB"
    },
    {
        question: "Which software prevents the external access to a system?",
        optionA: "Firewall",
        optionB: "Gateway",
        optionC: "Router",
        optionD: "Virus checker",
        answer: "optionA"
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following is a valid email address?",
        optionA: "javat@point.com",
        optionB: "gmail.com",
        optionC: "point@.com",
        optionD: "javatpoint@books",
        answer: "optionA"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following best describes uploading information?",
        optionA: "Sorting data on a disk drive",
        optionB: "Sending information to a host computer",
        optionC: "Receiving information from a host computer",
        optionD: "Sorting data on a hard drive",
        answer: "optionB"
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following is the most common internet protocol?",
        optionA: "HTML",
        optionB: "NetBEUI",
        optionC: "TCP/IP",
        optionD: "IPX/SPX",
        answer: "optionC"
    },
    {
        question: "Software programs that allow you to legally copy files and give them away at no cost are called which of the following?",
        optionA: "Probe ware",
        optionB: "Timeshare",
        optionC: "Shareware",
        optionD: "Public domain",
        answer: "optionD"
    },
    {
        question: "The term FTP stands for?",
        optionA: "File transfer program",
        optionB: "File transmission protocol",
        optionC: "File transfer protocol",
        optionD: "File transfer protection",
        answer: "optionC"
    }
]